https://www.jam-software.com/company/privacy.shtml

More
Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?
The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.
How do we collect your data?
Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form. Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.
What do we use your data for?
Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.
What rights do you have regarding your data?
You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.
When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. Detailed information can be found in the following privacy policy. You can object to this analysis. We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.
The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.
Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.
The party responsible for processing data on this website is:
JAM Software GmbH
Am Wissenschaftspark 26
54296 Trier
Germany
Managing Director: Joachim Marder
VAT ID: DE234825349
Commercial register number: HRB 4920 (AG Wittlich)
Phone: +49-651-145653-0
Fax: +49-651-145653-29
Email: info2@jam-software.com
The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).
Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email or message via our contact form making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
If there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link:
https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html.
This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.
If you enter into a contract which requires you to send us your payment information (e.g. account number for direct debits), we will require this data to process your payment. Payment transactions using common means of payment (Visa/MasterCard, direct debit) are only made via encrypted SSL or TLS connections. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line beginning with "https://" and the lock icon in your browser line is visible. In the case of encrypted communication, any payment details you submit to us cannot be read by third parties.
As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice or using our contact form if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.
We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.
We have appointed a data protection officer for our company.
Rainer Faldey
Data protection officer GDDcert. EU
Certified data protection officer EU GDPR
DSB Rainer Faldey
Im Handwerkerhof 1
54338 Schweich
Telephone: 06502-6019061
Email: rainer.faldey@datenschutz-trier.com
Some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. They help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser.
Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site. You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website. Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.
The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:
Browser type and browser version
Operating system used
Referrer URL
Host name of the accessing computer
Time of the server request
IP address
These data will not be combined with data from other sources. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
Should you send us questions via the contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including the contact details you provide, to answer your question and any follow-up questions. We do not share this information without your permission. We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will retain the data you provide on the contact form until you request its deletion, revoke your consent for its storage, or the purpose for its storage no longer pertains (e.g. after fulfilling your request). Any mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain unaffected by this provision.
You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here. The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory information requested during registration must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your registration. To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the email address specified during registration. We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.
We collect, process, and use personal data only insofar as it is necessary to establish, or modify legal relationships with us (master data). This is done based on Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract. We collect, process and use your personal data when accessing our website (usage data) only to the extent required to enable you to access our service or to bill you for the same. Collected customer data shall be deleted after completion of the order or termination of the business relationship. Legal retention periods remain unaffected.
We transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of your contract, for example, to companies entrusted to deliver goods to your location or banks entrusted to process your payments. Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do so. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
We transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of your contract with us, for example, to banks entrusted to process your payments. Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do so. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.
If a user of our software products reports an error, problem, request or suggestion for improvement, a ticket may get created for this in our internal issue tracker. The name, e-mail address and customer number of the customer may be stored together with the ticket in order to be able to make queries about the problem later. The customer data will be deleted 3 years after the ticket has been closed in the system.
This website uses Matomo (www.matomo.org) for web analytics, a software provided by InnoCraft Ltd., 150 Willis St, 6011 Wellington, New Zealand. Matomo enables an analysis of the use of the website. The information is transmitted to our web server located in Germany and stored there. We have a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize our website. We have activated the IP anonymization feature on this website. Your IP address will be shortened prior to transmission and saving. Matomo will use this information to evaluate your use of the website and to compile reports on website activity. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Matomo Analytics will not be merged with any other data.
Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data using Matomo (Piwik)
To prevent your visits to be collected from the web analytics at this site you can change settings following this link: Settings Webanalytics.
This website uses Google Ads and the Google remarketing feature combined with the cross-device capabilities. Ads is an online advertising program from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"). As part of Google Ads, we use so-called conversion tracking. Only after you click on one of our ads served by Google, a conversion tracking cookie and the remarketing feature is set. We instructed Google to anonymize all IP addresses.
Cookies are small text files that your internet browser stores on your computer. These cookies expire after 30 days and are not used for personal identification of the user. Should the user visit certain pages of the website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and the website can tell that the user clicked on the ad and proceeded to that page.† The information obtained using the conversion cookie is used to create conversion statistics. We do not obtain any information that can be used to personally identify users.
The remarketing feature enables to link target audiences for promotional marketing created with Google Remarketing to the cross-device capabilities of Google Ads. This allows advertising to be displayed based on your personal interests, identified based on your previous usage and surfing behavior on one device (e.g. your mobile phone), on other devices (such as a tablet or computer). Once you have given your consent, Google will associate your web and app browsing history with your Google Account for this purpose. That way, any device that signs in to your Google Account can use the same personalized promotional messaging.
If you do not want to participate in tracking, you can opt-out of this by disabling the Google Conversion Tracking cookie by changing your browser settings. In doing so, you will not be included in the conversion tracking statistics. Conversion cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. We have a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both our website and our Google advertising.
You can also configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
You can permanently opt out of cross-device remarketing/targeting by turning off personalized advertising in your Google Account; follow this link: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/. The aggregation of the data collected in your Google Account data is based solely on your consent, which you may give or withdraw from Google per Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO.
For more information and the Google Privacy Policy, go to: https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/.
Only after you click on one of our ads served by Bing this website uses Bing UET tags. This is a code that is used to store some non-personal data about the use of the website in connection with a cookie. Bing UET tags are a service of Microsoft Corporation (One Microsoft Way Redmond, WA 98052-6399, USA). For more information on Bing's analysis services, please visit the Bing Ads website:
https://help.bingads.microsoft.com/#apex/3/en/n5012/2.
For more information about Microsoft's and Bing's privacy practices, see the Microsoft Privacy Policy:
https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement.
Control and Deactivate Bing UET (Bing Universal Event Tracking) tags
To control the ads delivered to you access the Bing Ads Preferences Manager: https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings.
If you would like to receive our newsletter, we require a valid email address as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified email address and that you agree to receive this newsletter. In addition, the country where you are living is required for the content can be tailored to your needs. No additional data is collected or is only collected on a voluntary basis. We only use this data to send the requested information and do not pass it on to third parties.
We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1) (a) DSGVO. You can revoke consent to the storage of your data and email address as well as their use for sending the newsletter at any time, e.g. through the "unsubscribe" link in the newsletter. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.
The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you cancel your subscription when said data will be deleted. Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. email addresses for the members area) remain unaffected.
No unsolicited advertising mail will be sent for promoting our services or products. If you only consented to receiving update notifications, JAM Software GmbH will inform you about free updates. You will receive neither additional emails with information about other software products nor the newsletter of JAM Software GmbH. If you register for our newsletter, you consent to receiving the quarterly newsletter and other relevant information and offers from JAM Software GmbH via email. JAM Software will track opening rates (download of embedded pictures) for its own statistical purposes but will not store any personal data.
You can revoke your consent at any time by clicking on the link "Unsubscribe" you find in each email. Alternatively, you can use our contact form for your unsubscribing. Cancelling the newsletters and information emails is free, although fees of your service provider might apply.
Our website uses plug-ins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. Although we are using the enhanced data protection mode, if you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plug-in, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. If you're logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube: https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy.
Our website accepts payments via PayPal. The provider of this service is PayPal (Europe) S.‡.r.l & Cie, S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg. If you select payment via PayPal, the payment data you provide will be supplied to PayPal based on Art. 6 (1) (a) (Consent) and Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO (Processing for contract purposes). You have the option to revoke your consent at any time with future effect. It does not affect the processing of data previously collected.
Our website accepts payments via P credit card. The provider of this service is die V÷B-ZVD Processing GmbH, Eckenheimer Landstraﬂe 242, 60320 Frankfurt, Deutschland. If you select payment via credit card, the payment data you provide will be supplied to V÷B-ZVD based on Art. 6 (1) (a) (Consent) and Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO (Processing for contract purposes). You have the option to revoke your consent at any time with future effect. It does not affect the processing of data previously collected.
This privacy policy is up to date and was last changed on June 22, 2018. It is subject to alterations. Changes will be published at this place and will be effective from the day of publication.
Privacy Information for Customers / Suppliers / Business Contacts
Download PDF
Privacy Information for Applicants (only in German)
Download PDF
We donít use marketing cookies. Functional cookies ensure a smooth performance of our website.
If you continue to use our services, you agree to the use of cookies. Data protection at JAM
OK
